Guide to the Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 1927-1974
Ross, Philip Collection of NLRB Documents
- 13-RC-6440; Midland Machine Company, 1959 (Box 343, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6441; Strand Baking Co., 1959 (Box 343, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6480; Chicago Pail Manufacturing Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6481; Henry Service Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6479; Oak Brand Ice Cream Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6482; Geiger Automatic Sales Co., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6483; F. K. Robesons, Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6484; Montgomery Elevator Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6485; Edelmann Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6486; Speigel, Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6488; Star Bottling Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6490; Connelly, Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6491; Pennsault Chemical Corporation, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6492; Kurman Company, D., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6493; Krambo Foods, Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6494; Northern Engineering & Design Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6495; Drenks Food Div. of Sunshine Biscuit Co., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6496; Eisner-Jewel Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6497; Leather Craft Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6498; Piper Hotel Company, Belmont Hotel, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6499; Outagamie Producers Coop, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6500; Stepan Chemical Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6501; Crotty Brothers, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6502; Mayer-Hughes Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6503; Crosley-Laughlin Division, American Hoist & Derrick Co., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6504; Knickerbocker Case Corporation, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6511; Eisner Food Stores, Co., Inc., Division of Jewel Tea, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6512; National Biscuit Company, et al., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6505; Robert Gair Co. Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6506; Esquire Products, Inc., 1959 (Box 344, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6507; Standard Oil Company (Indiana), 1959 (Box 344, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6508; Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6509; Service Printers Incorporated, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6510; Jewel Tea Company, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 344, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6530; Schmidt Co., E. F., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6531; Dean Milk Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6532; T-H Products, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6533; Alexander Chemical & Nor. American Car Terminal, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6534; Roy E. Roth Company Turbine Pump Division, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6535; Linde Company, Division of Union Carbide Corp., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6537; Marblehead Lime Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6524; George Banta Publishing Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6525; Simmons Company, Living Room Furniture Division, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6526; Fuller-Goodman Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6527; B&N Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6528; Boulder Parts Corporation, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6529; J. C. Penney Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6536; Momence Manufacturing Corporation, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6514; Fox River Tool Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6515; Sherry Motors, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6516; Scot Industries, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6517; Holiday Transformer Corporation, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6518; Gateway Liquor Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6519 & 13-RC-6520; Krier Preserving Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6521; Crotty Brothers, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6522; Paramount Die Mold Co., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6523; Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6538; Schoolway Transportation Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6539; Avis Hotel, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6540; Hy-Tex Brick Co. (Hydraulic Press Brick Co.), 1959 (Box 345, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6541; P. A. Starck Piano Co., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6543; Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6544; Leek Proof, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6545; Midwest Products Co. Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6546; Jewel Tea Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6548; No-Pak, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6547; A&P Tea Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6549; Screencraft, Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6550; D'Amico Macaroni Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6551; We-Toast Bread Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6552; Florsheim Shoe Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 37)
- 13-RC-6553; Scott Burr Store Corp., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 38)
- 13-RC-6554; Magnus Metal Division of National Lead Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 39)
- 13-RC-6555; Sinclair Refining Co., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 40)
- 13-RC-6556; American Can Company, 1959 (Box 345, Folder 41)
- 13-RC-6557; Own a Home Trailer Inc., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 42)
- 13-RC-6558; Milwaukee Cheese Co., 1959 (Box 345, Folder 43)
- 13-RC-6615; American Bridge Division of United States Steel Corporation, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6616; Clatton Mark & Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6617; Strongin & Sons, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6618; Burmeister Plant - Chain Belt Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6620; General Loose Leaf Bindery, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6621; Clark Equipment Company, Brown Trailer Division, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6622; Gaylord Container Corp., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6606; Fun, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6607; Fred Leemhuis, Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6608; Domore Chair Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6609; Indiana Broadcasting Corporation, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6610; Rock Island County Beer Distributing Association, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6611; R&M Kaufmann, Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6612; Libby Mc Neill & Libby, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6613; Pittsburgh Plate Glass Co., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6614; Montgomery Ward & Co., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6596; Continental Baking Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6597; Montgomery Ward & Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6599; Reliable Furniture Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6600; Meyers Drug Stores, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6601; Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6602; Moxness Products, Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6603; Elliott Paint & Varnish Co., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6605; Doering Super Valu Market, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6623; Nick Beucher & Sons Co., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6624; Chicago Foam Products, Corp., Jetfoam Industries, Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6625; Mary J. Papson, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6626; Midwest Food Service, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6628; Evans Auto Service, Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6629; Knoblock Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6630; Bohn Aluminum & Brass Corporation, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6631; Rand McNally Corporation, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6632; Jewel Tea Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 346, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6633; Reiss Steamship Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6334; International Harvest Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6635; Western Printing & Lithographing Company, 1959 (Box 346, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6302; Red Owl Stores, Inc., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6305; Richardson Rod & Reel Company M-B Division, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6306; Reliable Electric Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6308; Universal Main Advertising Service Co., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6309; Jaeger Oldsmobile, Inc., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6310; Douglas Motors Corp., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6311; Dossinger Optical Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6312; K&W Battery Co., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6313; Midwest Lamp & Novelty, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6316; Hartung Motor Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6317; Cook Chocolate Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6318; Cudahy Tanning Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6320; American Hair & Felt Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6321; Plains Television Corp., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6322; Superior Welding Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6323; Krambo Food Stores Division Kroger Co., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6234; Sangamo Electric Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6325; Consolidated Walt & Inc., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6326; City Bottle Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6328; Melville's Choe Corp. Thomcan Div., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6329; Capodice & Sons, M., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6330; Eureka Specialty Printing Co. of Illinois, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6331; Bastian-Blessing Co., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6332; Wisconsin Rubber Products Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6333; Rollins Broadcasting, Inc., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6334; Western Electric Company Hawthorne Station, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6335; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Champaign #10), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6336; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Paxton), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6337; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Watskia), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6338; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Rossville), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6339; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Sheldon), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6340; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Potomic), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6341; Mr. Ernest Paxton (Rantoul), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6342; Mr. Ernest Paxton (Champaign Rt. 150), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6343; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Milford), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6344; Mr. Ernest C. Paxton (Hoopeston), 1959 (Box 347, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6345; Racine Heat Treating Company, 1959 (Box 347, Folder 37)
- 13-RC-6346; \ Peterson Co., 1959 (Box 347, Folder 38)
- 13-RC-6442; Improved Sponging Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6443; Harding - Williams, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6445; Midwest Food Service, James Elliott, American Can Co., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6478; Eisner Food Stores Division of Jewel Tea Co., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6472; Krambo, Division of Kroger Co., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6450; Reichhold Chemicals Inc., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6444; Modine Manufacturing Co., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6446; Midwest Food Service Chicago Screw Co. Cafeteria, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6447; Harding-Williams Company, Northern Illinois Gas Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6448; Harding Williams Co., Public Service Co. Cafeteria, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6463; Carter Machine & Tool Co., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 11)
- 14-RC-6449; Chicago North Side Newspapers, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6451; National Gypsum Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6452; Faber Industries Hide Plant, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6453; Aelco Foundries Inc., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6455; Harding-Williams, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6456; Ackerman Printing Co., G. A., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6457; Great Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6458; Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6459; Standard Oil Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6460; Brass Foundry Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6461; Cities Service Oil Company Marketing Division, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6462; Cohen Brothers Inc., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6464; Artag Plastics Corporation, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6466; Obligato, Charles & Sons, Inc., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6467; Farm Equipment Sales Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6468; Cavallini, Charles, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6469; Continental Nipple Mfg. Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6470; United Rawhide Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6471; Olin Mathiesen Chemical Corporation, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6473; Brandt Automatic Cashier Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6474; Standard Oil Company (Indiana), 1959 (Box 348, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6475; Hurwich Iron Company, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6476; Eagle-Picher Co., 1959 (Box 348, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6477; Blue Star Auto Stores, 1959 (Box 348, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6260; Union Tank Car Company, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6261; Gartland Steamship Co., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6265; Wyman Gordon Co. (Ingalls-Shepard Division), 1959 (Box 349, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6267; W. T. Grant Co., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6272; Royal Mfg. Co., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6274; Dearborn Electronic Laboratories, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6276; Rhoda's Trucking Service, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6278; Hazelriggs, Inc., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6286; Barnes Metal Products Company, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6282; Gould National Batteries, Inc., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6282; Gould National Batteries, Inc. - Extra Copies, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6285; Pure Sealed Dairy, Inc., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6289; Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6290; Robbins Plastic Machinery Corporation, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6291; Nodell Cadillac, Inc., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6293; Peerless Plastics Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6294; Harnischfeger Corporation, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6295; M&M Research Engineering, Inc., 1959 (Box 349, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6296; National Biscuit Company, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6297; Golblatts, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6301; Crosby Aeromarine Company, Subsidiary of Archer-Daniels-Midland Company, 1959 (Box 349, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-5646; Runzel Cord & Wire Co., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6647; Kearny & Trecker Corporation, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6648; Barber-Greene Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6637; Fisher Metal Products Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6640; Pepsi Cola Champaign-Urbana Bottling Co., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6641; Henry Weis Manufacturing Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6642; LAABS, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6643; Poston Brick Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6644; American Motors Corporation, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6645; Milwaukee Forge & Machine Co., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6649; Gary Steel Supply Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6650; Hanna Engineering Works, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6651; Strange Carton Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6652; Ruby Supplies, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6653; Madison Motors, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6654; Process Corporation, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6655; Cargill, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6656; Schoolway Transportation Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6657; Kam Kap Incorporated, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6658; Magnavox Laboratory, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6659; Piggly Wiggly Midwest Co., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6660; Crystal Preforming & Packaging, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6661; Superior Carton Corp., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6662; Baker Liquor Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6663; H. B. Ziffrin Sales Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6664; Jays Foods, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6665; Tremax Industries, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6666; Henderson, H. R., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6667; Stiger Precision Products, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6668; Helicopter Air Lift, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6669; Braun Lumber Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6670; Conron Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6671; Atlantic & Pacific Tea Company, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6672; Land Air, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6673; Wayne Cooperative Milk Producers, Inc., 1959 (Box 350, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6674; Seidler News Agency, 1959 (Box 350, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6682; Dobbs Houses, Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6683; Conrad Corporation, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6684; Peoria Board of Trades, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6688; Replogle Globes, Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6689; Scientific Industrial Supply Co., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6697; South Bend Foundry Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6698; Carl Zoll Stone Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6690; Barber Colman Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6691; Combined Locks Paper Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6692; Dawe's Laboratories, Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6693; Rollins Broadcasting, Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6694; Continental Scale Corporation, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6695; Chicago City Plating Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6696; Red Owl Stores, Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6675; Premalux Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6676; Joliet Marine Supply & Repair Service, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6677; Seidel Thiele Tannery Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6679; Solo Cup Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6680; Josten Ring Co., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6681; Chevrolet Saginaw Grey Iron Foundry, Division of General Motors Corp., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6699; Apex Coil & Transformer Corporation, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6700; Century Hardware Corporation, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6701; United Grain Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6702; Atlantic & Pacific Tea Co., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6703; United Grain Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6704; Conveyor Systems, Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6705; Eisner Food Stores, Division of Jewel Tea Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6706; Acme Gear Co., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6707; R. C. A. Service Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6708; Armour & Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6709; Firestone Stores, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6710; Rifz Craft, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6712; Lemont Mfg. Corp., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6713; Plibrico - Incinerator Division, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6714; Plibrico, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6715; Perfection Spring Manufacturing Co., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6716; Admiral Toy Corp., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 37)
- 13-RC-6717; Kellys Food Products, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 38)
- 13-RC-6718; Chicago Foundry Co., 1959 (Box 351, Folder 39)
- 13-RC-6719; Pegwill Packing Company, 1959 (Box 351, Folder 40)
- 13-RC-6764; Demert Dougherty, Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 1)
- 13-RC-6763; Knoedler Manufacturers, Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 2)
- 13-RC-6767; Continental Filling Corporation, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 3)
- 13-RC-6762; Jewel Tea Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 4)
- 13-RC-6771; Calumet Industrial & Farm Supply Co., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 5)
- 13-RC-6775; Cudahy Packing Co. (Rockford, Illinois Branch), 1959 (Box 352, Folder 6)
- 13-RC-6777; F. A. Lobdell & Son, Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 7)
- 13-RC-6772; Wareham-Hudson Dairy, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 8)
- 13-RC-6778; Jo-Carroll Electric Cooperative, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 9)
- 13-RC-6773; South Bend Tackle Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 10)
- 13-RC-6779; Metro Electro Processing Corp., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 11)
- 13-RC-6780; Combined Locks Paper Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 12)
- 13-RC-6774; International Expediters, Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 13)
- 13-RC-6770; Derges Bottling Co., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 14)
- 13-RC-6769; Peoria Area Certified Television & Appliance Dealers Association, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 15)
- 13-RC-6766; Indiana Meal Products Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 16)
- 13-RC-6765; Montgomery Ward, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 17)
- 13-RC-6783; Seaway Container Corporation, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 18)
- 13-RC-6788; Cabot, Carbon Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 19)
- 13-RC-6784; Waste Trade Industry of Chicago, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 20)
- 13-RC-6785; National Video Corporation, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 21)
- 13-RC-6786; Monumental Life Ins. Co., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 22)
- 13-RC-6787; C&S Plating Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 23)
- 13-RC-6789; Grotnes Machine Works, Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 24)
- 13-RC-6790; Belvidere Corporation, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 25)
- 13-RC-6791; Thompson Hayward Co., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 26)
- 13-RC-6792; Columbia Ribbon & Carbon Mfg. Co., Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 27)
- 13-RC-6795; Safer Foods Super Market, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 28)
- 13-RC-6796; Safer Foods Super Market, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 29)
- 13-RC-6797; Vulcan Container Incorporated, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 30)
- 13-RC-6798; Armstrong Cork Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 31)
- 13-RC-6800; Churchill Cabinet Co., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 32)
- 13-RC-6801; Russo Macaroni Co., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 33)
- 13-RC-6802; A. O. Smith Corporation, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 34)
- 13-RC-6803; American Bakeries Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 35)
- 13-RC-6805; Falls Products Incorporated, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 36)
- 13-RC-6807; V. La Rosa & Sons, Inc., 1959 (Box 352, Folder 37)
- 13-RC-6808; Kohlsville Cheese Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 38)
- 13-RC-6809; Century Hardware Corporation, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 39)
- 13-RC-6810; National Food Stores, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 40)
- 13-RC-6811; Montgomery Ward & Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 41)
- 13-RC-6812; Jewett & Sherman Company, 1959 (Box 352, Folder 42)
- 17-RC-2940; Dodge City Terminal Elevator Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 1)
- 17-RC-2941; Alton Box Board Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 2)
- 17-RC-2942; Zuzich Truck Line, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 3)
- 17-RC-2943; Atlas Bag Company, Incorporated, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 4)
- 17-RC-2947; Burlington Truck Lines, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 5)
- 17-RC-2944; Frontier Chemical Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 6)
- 17-RC-2945; Metal Finishers, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 7)
- 17-RC-2946; J. P. Gilman Granite Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 8)
- 17-RC-2948; Lily Tulip Cup Corp., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 9)
- 17-RC-2921; Kuhlham Diecasting Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 10)
- 17-RC-2923; Dorfman Plumbing Supply Company, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 11)
- 17-RC-2922; Griffin Wheel Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 12)
- 17-RC-2924; Van de Kamp's Holland Dutch Bakery Division, General Baking Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 13)
- 17-RC-2926; Montgomery Ward & Co., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 14)
- 17-RC-2927; Friendship Lanterns, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 15)
- 17-RC-2928; Wire Rope Corporation of America, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 16)
- 17-RC-2929; Valentine Manufacturing, Inc., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 17)
- 17-RC-2930; Rome Hotel, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 18)
- 17-RC-2931; Blackstone Hotel, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 19)
- 17-RC-2932; Zellinkoff Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 20)
- 17-RC-2933; Carpenter Paper Company, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 21)
- 17-RC-2934; Standard Oil Company of Indiana, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 22)
- 17-RC-2935; Puritan Manufacturing Co., 1959 (Box 353, Folder 23)
- 17-RC-2936; Morris Bell & Nathan Bell, d/b/a Longwear Paint & Varnish Works, 1959 (Box 353, Folder 24)